One time, look up!
Yeah!
Hello, everyone!
We are Nadayarumi!
This time, we would like to choose the member who knows the most about Nacchan!
Yay!
Yay! I'm so happy!
I'm so happy. Are you quite confident?
Yes!
Yes, I do!
Everyone is like...
Oh, I'm participating in this project for the first time!
You think you can do it.
It's pretty difficult.
That's true.
Because it's Nacchan, the difficulty level is 3 times higher than usual.
No, no, no, it's easy, easy.
It's not good.
Don't worry.
I've done King Honda, King Nagata, and King Suganami.
I participated in King Suganami.
I was the last.
Oh, no!
Let's make this one Natsune Kawaguchi.
That's right.
Nice to meet you.
Let's do that.
Yes, ma'am.
Let's get right to it!
Here is the first question!
What is your favorite movie?
I'll take that as a yes.
A movie column?
You're working, right?
I'll go with...
Nacchan, look who it is.
Karako.
If it's a drama, you'll know it right away.
What's your favorite drama?
I can't decide on just one movie.
What?
The one I've seen the most.
Wait a minute.
That's a lot.
That's a lot of work.
Wow, I don't know what I'm going to do.
I'm working on it right now.
Is it a movie?
I'll do a voice-over.
I really couldn't do one voice.
It's impossible.
I'll do it.
All right, let's open the doors!
Se-no!
Yes!
Stranger singles.
Harry Potter 1 and...
Single?
Oh, it fits. It fits.
Yes, but...
But that's my favorite drama that Nacchan just mentioned.
Oh, so it's a drama.
Oh, no, no, no!
I'll watch it next time.
No, no, no, no.
It's too different.
Correct me if I'm wrong.
The one I've seen the most times is
Charlie and the Chocolate Course.
I'm a little lost.
I was lost too.
Lost?
I always loved Harry Potter, too.
Of course you do.
That's why I couldn't decide on just one.
So I decided to go with the movie with the most episodes.
I'm sure I heard that word the other day.
What?
Zero points?
Oh, zero points.
Well, of course.
Now, here is the second question.
What is Natsune Kawaguchi's charm point?
Yes, she has many.
So many!
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
Her upper body?
What?
It's on your body to begin with.
Uh, yeah.
You know what, I'm going to go with looks.
I can give you a visual.
Visuals, please.
By the way, do you think you'll be right?
I think so.
Then this one.
What, like a dare?
Like a normal one?
I don't know.
It's a twist.
Yeah, I know.
One.
This is fun.
It's fun.
Cute. Fun.
Okay, this way.
Okay.
That's it!
Big dark eyes
Height
Big bent finger joints
Ah!
You say that a lot.
You do say that, don't you?
You're right.
Correct answer, please.
What's your charm?
Eyeballs.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
That's why.
Momochi's right.
Yay!
If it was just her eyes, it would be wrong.
But since you said "black eyes"...
That's a good answer.
Yay!
Wait, I just told Nacchan the other day that her eyes are big.
But they're really big.
Just a little.
Eyes?
They're cute, too.
I thought it would be a twist.
You're right.
This one.
Yes, yes.
This one's amazing, too.
Maybe it's a skill.
Oh, I see... Charm points.
One point for Momoqun.
Yay!
Next time!
Question 3 is this way.
I don't like this Natsune Kawaguchi.
What kind?
She's pretty much a comic relief type, isn't she?
You're a comedy type, aren't you?
Yes...
That's right.
But it's a little bit... unfunny.
It's a constant day.
I don't know.
What's up with the relentless day?
No, it's not.
What about the never-ending day?
It's a never-ending day.
Here are the titles for the three of us.
Natsume Kawaguchi has lost her sense of humor
Natsume Kawaguchi, who is short-tempered
Unhappy expedition captain
Yes! Maybe he's a bit of a daredevil.
Maybe it's a good idea. Maybe it's a good idea.
Then give us the correct answer.
I always walk backwards when I walk.
Wait a minute.
I'm not saying I don't like it or anything. Wait a minute.
Walking backwards?
Yeah, like this.
It's not that it's hard.
Unhappy is good.
Thank you very much.
But zero points.
That's disappointing. This one didn't really hit me.
Okay, question 4, please.
Draw the character you like best.
As expected...
What's that? Huh? Hi-chan? Huh?
My favorite character.
I'll take no hints on this one. Is this it?
Okay? Yes. Is it okay? Here are the three's answers.
Natsuranbo, Natsuranbo, Natsuranbo, Natsuranbo, Natsuranbo, Natsuranbo, Natsuranbo. Correct!
Ha-ha-ha-ha...
It's "Janratzlambo"!
no lo my mother is scuttling avil thank you
saker
I typed two images and it was about tus!
Yay! Then, the fifth question, please.
Please sing something What did you sing?
What did you sing? What was it?
What was it?
Oh, the one you were worried about?
Oh, you're so cute, you're so cute.
I don't know what's going on anymore.
Is the answer a good answer?
I don't know.
Oh, my God!
I'll start from the point where I see it.
Well, I guess I'll just have to...
Oh, it's possible.
Here's the destination I had a feeling about.
Surely I am Kawaguchi Natsune's song
I wrote three lyrics on the spot... to Natsune Kawaguchi's song.
I see.
Do you get it?
This is mine.
Rururururu.
Yes, like humming.
I know, right?
And I already thought I made it.
I think it's my own work.
I think it was thought up with words
Well, here's the answer.
This way.
this way.
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
But Momo...
0.5 points.
Aah! Really?
Yes!
But, come on.
Here.
Two points.
Isn't that the song about the tuna with the face-print?
No, it's not.
I don't know why I drank it, so when I lost it...
Yeah, that's too bad.
Okay, 0.5 and 0.2 points.
Yes!
And so, the sixth question.
What song would you like Momo Sakurai to sing?
Hee!
There's no limit to the number of songs like that!
Infinite!
Um, seriously.
He wants Momo to sing that version of Noiney's song.
I want it!
I keep saying it.
I can't get it.
Can you come outside?
I'm feeling pretty paranoid.
They're all singing this girl's voice to me.
I know, right?
That's what I often think.
I don't know.
ok then, what's the meeting of the 3 of us?
Freeze Miniska Postwoman
Let's go to the holobar stage, iq 2 ea
I want to join solo this song is because I like Nacchan so I like Nacchan by halopro
I like Nacchan by Halo Pro I want to go in this song because I like Nacchan by Halo Pro I want to go in this song because I like Nacchan by Halo Pro I like Nacchan by Cyber Guidon
I'm so happy for you!
I'm so happy to hear that I'm so happy to hear that I'm so happy to hear that I'm so happy to hear that I'm so happy to hear that
I just got the offi feed... and it's not the full version... just the first verse...
I want to sing the full song, please!
I'd like to sing the full song, please.
Perala lu nu!
I don't Нее Yes, you do
7...
to the eye
Thе resumes оf thе loans аrе anterior to thе letter "F".
I'm not sure if it's a loan, but I'm sure it's a loan.
I've been in the museum before, Claudi!
You've recorded the words for me before, haven't you?
You don't remember?
You said you were going to compliment me for the next two minutes.
If you remember that...
I'll pretend to be Nacchan.
I'll be Nacchan and sing your praises.
Yes.
First of all, Milten is cute.
He's so sweet, he's so sweet.
Her teeth are white.
Her legs are really thin.
She has a lovely voice and singing voice.
And, oh, she looks good in a pantyhose.
That's all.
Thank you.
That's it.
She talks like this.
Yeah.
Okay, I'll go.
Oh, my God, Milten is so sweet.
She's the nicest girl I've ever met.
She has such a kind heart.
And then there's her face.
He's really cute at the top of the class, and you love him.
And I really admire him for his bluff.
Yes, I do.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm going to talk for a moment like this.
Well, let's go to the milten.
I'll go.
You're so cute.
He's so cute.
I love it.
Come here.
Praise, praise, praise.
Oh, wow.
I think I might have one of those.
Then please answer me.
MIRTEN Really...
Really, Milten.
He's so kind-hearted and funny.
His eyes are this big.
He's so cute!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I see.
I'm so happy!
Momoken is amazing.
Really?
He has a good heart.
Yes, he's a sweet boy.
Yes, a great image.
This is a great image of Momoken, too.
One point.
Yay!
That's good!
1 point for Momochan!
That's great!
Yay!
I might have been asleep.
When I was talking...
I got about 7.5 points.
Oh, no.
Minus.
Why not?
Minus 1 point
Ha-ha-ha!
Did I have 1 point?
Why did you do that?
Because I made fun of you.
Momochan got 1 point.
Thank you very much.
Suzuki, minus one point.
What's the score for Omari?
Milten 1.2
Ah, yay!
1.2
Hi-chan is 0
Fan
A-ha-ha!
It got better.
Momoken got a 3.5.
Isn't that great?
Wait a minute.
Is there such a thing as 100 points?
If you don't miss the next question by a minute, maybe I'll give you 100 points.
Ehhhhh...
Let's go for it!
And now, the last problem, please.
Haa...
Please scold me as if you were Hitomi Suzuki's mother.
I don't mean to imitate my mom
When you're my mother...
What do you mean?
If you were to scold me, what would you say?
Right.
Serious.
Zero points from me.
That's pretty much my mom.
My mom scolded me.
By the way, what do you scold my mom for?
life
Ehhhh...
I feel bad.
If you were to get angry at me, I think this is the only thing you would do.
Na-nae...
Okay, let's start with Momokun.
Here we go.
Ri-chan, you're spreading your luggage too thin.
I'm sorry.
Sure thing.
Get on with it.
Let's go.
I'll go.
Ri-chan, how long are you sleeping?
Wake up.
Hey!
You're so sweet.
You're both so sweet.
I'll go.
You've been drinking a lot of Coke.
You're all hot and sweaty, and you need to calm down.
Okay.
What the hell is this and not this?
What's your answer?
I think I got it right.
You always call me when I'm scared.
This one...
Don't say it!
I'm not angry at all.
There's nothing to be mad about.
You're so sweet.
I'm calling you when you're cute.
It's nighttime. I'm scared.
But you said he's nocturnal.
So I'm like, "Yeah, I'll call him.
We stayed on the phone together.
He helped me take off my makeup.
Heh...
I'm afraid I can't move at night.
Oh, my.
I'm sorry.
You're scared.
You're so cute.
Thank you for everything.
Okay, well, this is...
One point for looking.
Oh, my God! You always give it to me?
Hi-chan, minus 10 points.
No?
Why? Why?
It was the easiest way to find out.
I didn't even pass.
Here are the final points
Momochan, 3.5 points.
Suzuki?
S10
S10, apparently.
Mirutens?
2.2 points
So the winner is Momochan!
You were so confident!
I'm so happy!
She's crying, she's crying!
Next time, I'll do my best not to get any negative points!
That's all for now, this is Hiroshi Kawaguchi.